cellphoneforums.net 2012-06-18

# Cell Phone Forums - Privacy Statement

Cell Phone Forums recognizes that you care about the personal information that obtained about you and how it is used. The following outlines the various ways Cell Phone Forums uses information to provide you a better browsing experience.

This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the Cell Phone Forums web site.

By registering to Cell Phone Forums you submit a chosen name and an e-mail address. No sensitive personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.

By registering and posting content to Cell Phone Forums you agree that you own or have been given permission to post content.

If you post content you continue to own this content but grant a license to Sugarman Studios, LLC and its affiliates to use and distribute said content.

Cell Phone Forums stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the web server, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from trusted internet sites, such as Cell Phone Forums. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)

Cell Phone Forums does not collect or sell personally identifiable information.

Cell Phone Forums will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant United States legislation.

All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your [User Control Panel](http://cellphoneforums.net/usercp.php).

You have a legal right for the personal information held at Cell Phone Forums to be updated, if it is incorrect, or removed from the site completely if you choose. This can be done through your [User Control Panel](http://cellphoneforums.net/usercp.php). If you are having issues with this, please [contact us](http://cellphoneforums.net/sendmessage.php) for assistance.

Cell Phone Forums will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.

This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA agreement is necessary.

This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, please [Contact Us](http://cellphoneforums.net/sendmessage.php)
